Game Objects are the items
ゲームオブジェクトとは
that make up your Unity scenes
Unity のシーンを構成するアイテムです。
Everything within a scene is considered a game object
シーンに含まれるすべてのものはゲームオブジェクトであり
and these objects are made up of a number of components.
これらのオブジェクトは複数のコンポーネントから構成されます。
Each has a necessary transform component
各々には Transform という必須コンポーネントがあり
that contains the position, rotation and scale of the game object.
これにはゲームオブジェクトの Postion, Rotation, Scale が含まれます。
Components can be added
コンポーネントの追加は
using the Add Component button at
インスペクタの最下部にある
the bottom of the inspector.
Add Component ボタンを使用します。
Or by using the Component top menu.
あるいはメニューから Component を選択する方法もあります。
Scripts are also considered as components
スクリプトはコンポーネントとして考えられ
and can be added using the aforementioned menus.
前述したメニューからも追加することが出来ます。
They can also be created and added using the Add Component button.
これららはさらに作成および追加することが可能であり
Components can be removed,
コンポーネントも削除したり、
or copy pasted using the cog icon to the right
コピー＆ペーストしたりするためにインスペクタの右にある
of their representation in the inspector.
歯車アイコンを使用します。
You can then select another object and paste them
次に別のオブジェクトを選択して歯車アイコンをクリックすることで
by clicking on the cog icon.
ペーストすることが出来ます。
You can also add a script to an object
オブジェクトにスクリプトを追加するには
by dragging it to the hierarchy
Hierarchy 上またはシーンビュー上の
or to the object in the scene view.
オブジェクトにドラッグします。
And you can even drag and drop to empty space in the inspector
さらにインスペクタ上の空いたスペースにドラッグ＆ドロップすることで
in order to add a script as a component.
スクリプトをコンポーネントとして追加することが出来ます。
Game objects are seen in the hierarchy view as a list,
ゲームオブジェクトは 親子関係をもった階層として
with a hierarchy of parent child relationships
Hierarchy ビューでリストとして表示されます。
demonstrated by arrows to the left of their name.
これは名前の左にある矢印で展開できます。
The Hierarchy is a list of all the game objects in the scene
Hierarchy はシーンにある全てのゲームオブジェクトの一覧であり、
and as such everything that you see in the scene view
このためシーンビューにみえる全ては
is also listed in the hierarchy.
さらにHierarchy にリスト表示されます。
And when selecting a game object in either view
そしていずれかのビューでゲームオブジェクトを選択すると
it's selected in both.
両方のビューで選択されます。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)